[{
	"question":"morning",
		"answer":"subha"
},
{
	"question":"night",
		"answer":"raat"
},
{
	"question":"hello",
		"answer":"namasthey"
},
{
	"question":"book",
		"answer":"kitab"
},
{
	"question":"computer",
		"answer":"kampyootar"
},
{
	"question":"ten",
		"answer":"das"
},
{
	"question":"question",
		"answer":"sawal"
},
{
	"question":"ocean",
		"answer":"samandar"
},
{
	"question":"glasses",
		"answer":"aaynak"
},
{
	"question":"tea",
		"answer":"chai"
}]